[
  {
    "name": "Basics I",
    "icon": "book",
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "description": "Learn some basic vocabulary and grammar.",
    "dictionary": ["han"],
    "unit": [
      [
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
            "word": "han",
            "tip": "[He/she/it] is the implied subject. If context demands it, [they] may be the implied subject.",
            "example": {
              "sentence": "[han].",
              "translation": "[He/she/it is]."
            }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "She exists.",
          "answers": ["han"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han.",
          "answers": ["to be", "he is", "she is", "it is", "they are", "to exist", "he exists", "she exists", "it exists", "they exist"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "symi",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "han [symi].",
            "translation": "He/she/it is [a man]."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "symi.",
          "answers": ["a man", "man"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "He is a man.",
          "answers": ["han symi"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "cévo",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "han [cévo].",
            "translation": "He/she/it is [a woman]."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "A woman.",
          "answers": ["cévo"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "Sylvie han cévo.",
          "answers": ["Sylvie is a woman"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "She is a woman.",
          "answers": ["han cévo"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "ele",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "cévo [ele] symi.",
            "translation": "A woman [and] a man."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "A man and a woman.",
          "answers": ["symi ele cévo"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "Mark and Amy are a man and a woman.",
          "answers": ["Mark ele Amy han symi ele cévo"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han cévo. han symi.",
          "answers": ["he is a woman he is a man", "she is a woman he is a man", "it is a woman he is a man", "he is a woman she is a man", "she is a woman she is a man", "it is a woman she is a man", "he is a woman it is a man", "she is a woman it is a man", "it is a woman it is a man"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "They are a man and a woman.",
          "answers": ["han symi ele cévo"]
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "mikol",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "David han [mikol] symi.",
            "translation": "David is a [short] man."
          },
          "tip": "Adjectives come before nouns."
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "mikol symi.",
          "answers": ["a short man", "short man", "a small man", "small man"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "They are small.",
          "answers": ["han mikol"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "náu",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "[náu] cévo.",
            "translation": "A [tall] woman."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "náu symi.",
          "answers": ["a tall man", "tall man", "a big man", "big man"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "She is tall.",
          "answers": ["han náu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "Michael is a short man and Naomi is a tall woman.",
          "answers": ["Michael han mikol symi ele Naomi han náu cévo."]
        },
        {
          "type": "match",
          "foreign": ["han", "symi", "cévo", "mikol", "náu"],
          "native": ["it is", "man", "woman", "short", "tall"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "ćina",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "cévo han [ćina].",
            "translation": "A woman is [a person]."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han mikol ćina.",
          "answers": ["he is a small person", "she is a small person", "it is a small person", "they are a small person", "he is a short person", "she is a short person", "it is a short person", "they are a short person"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "Amy is a tall person.",
          "answers": ["Amy han náu ćina"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "Sarah han náu.",
          "answers": ["Sarah is large", "Sarah is big", "Sarah is tall"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han mikol ele náu.",
          "answers": ["he is small and big", "she is small and big", "it is small and big", "they are small and big", "he is short and big", "she is short and big", "it is short and big", "they are short and big", "he is small and large", "she is small and large", "it is small and large", "they are small and large", "he is short and large", "she is short and large", "it is short and large", "they are short and large", "he is small and tall", "she is small and tall", "it is small and tall", "they are small and tall", "he is short and tall", "she is short and tall", "it is short and tall", "they are short and tall"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "Jordan exists.",
          "answers": ["Jordan han"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "He is short.",
          "answers": ["han mikol"]
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "ny",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "[ny] han náu ćina.",
            "translation": "[I] am a tall person"
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "It is me.",
          "answers": ["han ny"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "I am Alex.",
          "answers": ["ny han Alex"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "ké",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "[ké] han cévo.",
            "translation": "[You] are a woman."
          },
          "tip": "[ké] can only be used as a subject (infront of the verb)."
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "You are tall.",
          "answers": ["ké han náu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ké han Daniel.",
          "answers": ["you are Daniel"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "vu",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "han [vu].",
            "translation": "He/she/it is [you]."
          },
          "tip": "[vu] can only be used as a object (after the verb)."
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ké han vu.",
          "answers": ["you are you"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "It is you.",
          "answers": ["han vu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
          "prompt": "han vu. ___ han náu.",
          "answer": "ké",
          "choices": ["ké", "vu", "mikol"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "téu",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "han [téu].",
            "translation": "it is [him/her/it/them]."
          },
          "tip": "[téu] may not be used as a subject of a sentence."
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "David is him.",
          "answers": ["David han téu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny han mikol.",
          "answers": ["I am short", "I am small"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "It is them.",
          "answers": ["han téu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ké han.",
          "answers": ["you are", "you exist"]
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny han mikol.",
          "answers": ["I am short", "I am small"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han náu.",
          "answers": ["he is tall", "she is tall", "it is tall", "they are tall", "he is big", "she is big", "it is big", "they are big", "he is large", "she is large", "it is large", "they are large"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "ćy",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "[ćy] han.",
            "translation": "[We] exist."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ćy han náu.",
          "answers": ["we are tall", "we are big", "we are large"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "We are short.",
          "answers": ["ćy han mikol"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "You are us.",
          "answers": ["ké han ćy"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "vun",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "[vun] han.",
            "translation": "[You] exist."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "You all are large.",
          "answers": ["vun han náu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "vun han mikol.",
          "answers": ["you are small", "you all are small", "you are short", "you all are short"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny han téu.",
          "answers": ["I am him", "I am her", "I am it"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "It is us.",
          "answers": ["han ćy"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "We are short.",
          "answers": ["ćy han mikol"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "sorón",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "ké han [sorón].",
            "translation": "You are [kind]."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "You are kind.",
          "answers": ["ké han sorón", "vun han sorón"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ćy han sorón",
          "answers": ["we are nice", "we are kind"]
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ćy han sorón.",
          "answers": ["we are nice", "we are kind"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han mikol.",
          "answers": ["he is short", "he is small", "she is short", "she is small", "it is short", "it is small", "they is short", "they is small"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "They are nice.",
          "answers": ["han sorón"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "You are her.",
          "answers": ["ké han téu", "vun han téu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han vun.",
          "answers": ["it is you", "they are you", "it is you all", "they are you all", "he is you all"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "He is a man.",
          "answers": ["han symi"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "It is us.",
          "answers": ["han ćy"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han vu.",
          "answers": ["it is you", "he is you", "she is you"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ké han symi.",
          "answers": ["you are a man"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "You are kind.",
          "answers": ["ké han sorón", "vun han sorón"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny han téu.",
          "answers": ["I am him", "I am her", "I am it"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han cévo.",
          "answers": ["he is a woman", "she is a woman", "it is a woman", "they are a woman"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "You are me.",
          "answers": ["ké han ny", "vun han ny"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny han náu.",
          "answers": ["I am tall", "I am big", "I am large"]
        }, 
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "Alexa and Sarah are them.",
          "answers": ["Alexa ele Sarah han téu."]
        }
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Basics II",
    "icon": "bridge-circle-exclamation",
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "description": "Learn the definite article, demonstratives, negation, and verb form.",
    "unit": [
      [
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "i",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "[i] cévo han sorón.",
            "translation": "[The] woman is kind."
          },
          "tip": "[i] can turn an adjective into a noun. (ex. [i náu] means [the tall one/thing])"
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "i symi.",
          "answers": ["the man"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "i náu.",
          "answers": ["the tall thing", "the big thing", "the large thing", "the tall one", "the big one", "the large one"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "It is her! She is the woman.",
          "answers": ["han téu han i cévo"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny han i symi.",
          "answers": ["I am the man"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "nes",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "i [nes].",
            "translation": "The [thing]."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "nes han náu.",
          "answers": ["a thing is tall", "thing is tall", "a thing is big", "thing is big", "a thing is large", "thing is large", "an object is tall", "object is tall", "an object is big", "object is big", "an object is large", "object is large"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "The thing exists. It is large!",
          "answers": ["i nes han han náu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "vé",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "i cévo [vé han] nes.",
            "translation": "The woman [has] a thing."
          },
          "tip": "Preverbs like [vé] must always be used before [han], unless otherwise mentioned."
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "i symi vé han nes.",
          "answers": ["the man has a thing", "the man has an object"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "vé han nes.",
          "answers": ["he has a thing", "she has a thing", "it has a thing", "they have a thing", "he has an object", "she has an object", "it has an object", "they have an object"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "She has a kind man. He is short.",
          "answers": ["vé han sorón symi han mikol"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "The man is the short one.",
          "answers": ["i symi han i mikol"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "i sorón han ny.",
          "answers": ["the kind thing is me", "the nice thing is me", "the kind one is me", "the nice one is me", "the kind thing is I", "the nice thing is I", "the kind one is I", "the nice one is I"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "You are the tall ones.",
          "answers": ["vun han i náu"]
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "The tall thing is a tall person.",
          "answers": ["i náu han náu ćina"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "vé han i sorón",
          "answers": ["he has the kind thing", "she has the kind thing", "it has the kind thing", "they have the kind thing", "he has the nice thing", "she has the nice thing", "it has the nice thing", "they have the nice thing", "he has the kind object", "she has the kind object", "it has the kind object", "they have the kind object", "he has the nice object", "she has the nice object", "it has the nice object", "they have the nice object", "he has the kind one", "she has the kind one", "it has the kind one", "they have the kind one", "he has the nice one", "she has the nice one", "it has the nice one", "they have the nice one"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "miro",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "ny vé han [miro].",
            "translation": "I have [(a loaf of) bread]."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ćy vé han miro.",
          "answers": ["we have bread", "we have a loaf of bread", "we have a bread loaf"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "You have the bread loaf.",
          "answers": ["ké vé han i miro", "vun vé han i miro"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "The bread is small.",
          "answers": ["i miro han mikol"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "i nes han miro.",
          "answers": ["the thing is bread", "the thing is a bread loaf", "the thing is a loaf of bread", "the object is bread", "the object is a bread loaf", "the object is a loaf of bread"]
        },
        {
          "type": "match",
          "foreign": ["miro", "ćina", "ćy", "han", "téu"],
          "native": ["bread", "person", "we", "to be", "him/her/it"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "The kind man has the bread.",
          "answers": ["i sorón symi vé han i miro"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "The short one is the woman.",
          "answers": ["i mikol han i cévo"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "lavat",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "vé han [lavat].",
            "translation": "he/she/it/they have [an apple]."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "i symi vé han i lavat.",
          "answers": ["the man has the apple"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han sorón mikol cévo.",
          "answers": ["he is a nice short woman", "he is a kind short woman", "he is a nice small woman", "he is a kind small woman", "she is a nice short woman", "she is a kind short woman", "she is a nice small woman", "she is a kind small woman", "it is a nice short woman", "it is a kind short woman", "it is a nice small woman", "it is a kind small woman", "they are a nice short woman", "they are a kind short woman", "they are a nice small woman", "they are a kind small woman"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ké han lavat.",
          "answers": ["you are an apple"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "The kind woman has the small loaf of bread.",
          "answers": ["i sorón cévo vé han i mikol miro"]
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "hotá",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "i cévo vé [hotá] i náu.",
            "translation": "the woman [does not] have the tall thing."
          },
          "tip": "In verb form, [hotá] replaces [han]."
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny vé hotá miro.",
          "answers": ["I do not have bread", "I do not have a loaf of bread", "I do not have a bread loaf"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "You are not an apple.",
          "answers": ["ké hotá lavat", "vun hotá lavat"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "Andrea hotá cévo.",
          "answers": ["Andrea is not a woman"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "Jake vé hotá mikol miro.",
          "answers": ["Jake does not have a small loaf of bread", "Jake does not have a small bread loaf"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "kas",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "i sorón ćina [kas] han i miro.",
            "translation": "The kind person [eats] the bread."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny kas han.",
          "answers": ["I eat", "I drink"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "She does not eat bread.",
          "answers": ["kas hotá miro"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "Kiera kas hotá.",
          "answers": ["Kiera does not eat", "Kiera does not drink"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "móu",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "kas han [móu].",
            "translation": "(He/she/it/they) drink [water]."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ké kas hotá móu.",
          "answers": ["you do not drink water"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "He does not have water.",
          "answers": ["vé hotá móu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "The woman drinks water.",
          "answers": ["i cévo kas han móu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ké kas han i mikol lavat.",
          "answers": ["you eat the small apple"]
        },
        {
          "type": "match",
          "foreign": ["kas", "ćina", "hotá", "móu", "i"],
          "native": ["to drink", "person", "to not", "water", "the"]
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "na",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "[na] symi han mikol.",
            "translation": "[This] man is small."
          },
          "tip": "Similar to the definite article, [i], demonstratives can turn an adjective into a noun. (ex. [na náu] means [this tall one/thing])"
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny vé hotá na nes.",
          "answers": ["I do not have this thing"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "This thing is tall.",
          "answers": ["na nes han náu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "This short person is Alex.",
          "answers": ["na mikol ćina han Alex"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "mu",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "[mu] cévo kas hotá miro.",
            "translation": "[That] woman does not eat bread."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "That woman is nice.",
          "answers": ["mu cévo han sorón"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "That person has water.",
          "answers": ["mu ćina vé han móu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "mu han téu.",
          "answers": ["that is him", "that is her", "that is it"]
        },
        {
          "type": "vocabulary",
          "word": "eu",
          "example": {
            "sentence": "na cévo hotá [eu].",
            "translation": "This woman is not [bad]."
          }
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny han eu.",
          "answers": ["I am bad"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han eu.",
          "answers": ["he is bad", "she is bad", "it is bad", "they are bad"]
        },
        {
          "type": "comprehension",
          "prompt": "Alex han symi ele Sarah han cévo. na symi han náu ele eu. na cévo han mikol ele sorón.",
          "question": "Who is the nice one?",
          "answer": "Sarah",
          "choices": ["Alex", "Sarah"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "na symi ele mu symi han mikol",
          "answers": ["this man and that man are small", "this man and that man are short"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "miro kas hotá",
          "answers": ["bread does not eat", "bread does not drink", "a loaf of bread does not eat", "a loaf of bread does not drink", "a bread loaf does not eat", "a bread loaf does not drink"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "na eu ćina han vu.",
          "answers": ["this bad person is you"]
        }
      ],
      [
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "Mark and Amy are a man and a woman.",
          "answers": ["Mark ele Amy han symi ele cévo"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "They are not bad.",
          "answers": ["hotá eu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "na eu ćina han vu.",
          "answers": ["this bad person is you"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "This thing is tall.",
          "answers": ["na nes han náu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "This short person is Alex.",
          "answers": ["na mikol ćina han Alex"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny han téu.",
          "answers": ["I am him", "I am her", "I am it"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "han cévo.",
          "answers": ["he is a woman", "she is a woman", "it is a woman", "they are a woman"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "Andrea hotá cévo.",
          "answers": ["Andrea is not a woman"]
        },
        {
          "type": "match",
          "foreign": ["miro", "ćina", "ćy", "han", "téu"],
          "native": ["bread", "person", "we", "to be", "him/her/it"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "Jake vé hotá mikol miro.",
          "answers": ["Jake does not have a small loaf of bread", "Jake does not have a small bread loaf"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "It is her! She is the woman.",
          "answers": ["han téu han i cévo"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "You are not an apple.",
          "answers": ["ké hotá lavat", "vun hotá lavat"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ny han i symi.",
          "answers": ["I am the man"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "The woman drinks water.",
          "answers": ["i cévo kas han móu"]
        },
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "foreign-native",
          "prompt": "ké kas han i mikol lavat.",
          "answers": ["you eat the small apple"]
        }
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Greetings and Questions",
    "icon": "file-circle-question",
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "description": "Learn introductions, question words, and question form.",
    "unit": [
      [
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "She eats",
          "answers": ["a"]
        }
      ]
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Undecided",
    "icon": "file-circle-question",
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "description": "Learn adjective form and noun cases.",
    "unit": [
      [
        {
          "type": "short-response",
          "direction": "native-foreign",
          "prompt": "kas hotá.",
          "answers": ["a"]
        }
      ]
    ]
  }
]
